Know your neighbors.
Welcome to Leith is a thriller, crime, documentary
film directed by Michael Beach Nichols.
In September 2012, the tiny prairie town of Leith, North
Dakota, sees its population of 24 grow by one.
As the new resident's behavior becomes more threatening, tensions soar, and the
residents desperately look for ways to expel their unwanted neighbor.
Himself, played by Craig Cobb.
Welcome to Leith is a 2015 American documentary film directed
by Michael Beach Nichols and Christopher K.
Walker about white supremacist Craig Cobb's attempt to
take over the North Dakota city Leith.
The film premiered on January 26, 2015 at the 2015 Sundance Film Festival and, after a limited theatrical
release on September 9, was broadcast on PBS' series Independent Lens on April 4, 2016.
The film explores themes of small town, racist, north
dakota, racism, white supremacists.
The tone is intense.